I'm going to offer up this loving correction for us because I think there's a short-sightedness that is so easy to happen because of the indoctrination that we all be under.
But I just want to throw this out there. Folks said they voted for this and turned their heads when people who are members of a cultural group are kidnapped and feel good about that because they said they didn't care about us.
So why should we care about them? And y'all same people don't understand why celebrating with a feast that is done in commemoration of the massacre of Native Americans is wildly, not only disrespectful, but hypocritical.
Imagine if Native Americans across the nation collectively sat down for a feast to commemorate the day that white folks sat down to eat the remains of Nat Turner after suppressing his slave rebellion.
And they did, by the way, they did eat him. If you as a person want people to care about you, you got to start by caring about them.
And if you are somebody that doesn't want to be continuously aligned and in support of and a receiver of the continued oppression of this nation,
then you can start by not celebrating any of its oppression, even if it's not about you.
We're going to fight with solidarity.
Listen to your people.
Because I'm in awe.
Billionaires should be scared of.